{"data":[{"question":"The people in general looked upon the situation ___.","a":"as critical","b":"to be critical","c":"being critical","d":"critical","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Look upon\/on as: to consider someone or something in a particular way, or as a particular thing","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Teaching and learning are part of the same educational experience, but unfortunately they are often thought of ___.","a":"to be separate","b":"as separate","c":"separate","d":"as to be separate","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Think of something as: to consider that someone or something is a particular thing or has a particular quality","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"You would become irritated if you watched the correspondence ___on your desk day by day.","a":"to pile up","b":"pile up","c":"to be piling up","d":"pile down","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb (with to) :you find \/see or watch the whole action \n- Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb_ing : you find \/see or watch part of the action","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Where did you see him ? \" I saw him ___ downtown last night.\"","a":"had worked","b":"had been working","c":"worked","d":"working","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb (with to) :you find \/see or watch the whole action \n- Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb_ing : you find \/see or watch part of the action","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"What did you do yesterday?. I saw a whale ___.","a":"to catch","b":"catch","c":"caught","d":"having caught","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Passive voice with some verbs : Find\/ see\/ watch...: \n- Find\/see\/watch + Object + Past participle","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Has Helen decided to argue with the instructor about her grades? \"No, she said she would ___\"","a":"let the matter resting","b":"let rest the matter","c":"let the matter rest","d":"let matter to rest","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Let something + Infinitive : To allow something to happen","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"What does he wish? \"He wishes ___\"","a":"he would cut his hair","b":"to have his hair cut","c":"cutting his hair","d":"to cut his hair","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Wish + To Verb \n- Passive voice: Have sth done","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"I don't understand that sentence. \"Let's get Tom ___ that sentence again.\"","a":"explain","b":"explained","c":"explaining","d":"to explain","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Get somebody to do something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"What can I do? \"Please get the lawn ___\"","a":"to be mowed","b":"to mow","c":"mowing","d":"mowed","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Passive voice: Get something done","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"What should we do now? \"Let's tell the taxi driver ___ for us here.\"","a":"waiting","b":"waited","c":"to wait","d":"to waited","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Tell sbd to do sth","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"}]}